Hello friends,
we heartily welcome you to Stock Market Trading.  If
you are visiting our channel for the first time,
please subscribe.  To get the latest and
genuine information, if you
subscribe then it will be your benefit.   If you do
not subscribe then how will you suffer the loss
because whatever we talk about here is the
latest and genuine information.
Where you can make money, earn something,
learn something.  Let's talk
about ICICI LBRD.  Yes, if we
talk about ICI LBRD, here the Q4
result has been out.  Before that let us
look at its chart.  What
is visible on the chart?  Here the support
is at the level.  If it
crosses this support level, it will definitely
give a good momentum.  But here it
depends on the result of Q4.  If the Q4 results are
good then no doubt a good
momentum and a good rise can be seen in it.  The
result of Q4 is wrong.
No doubt selling pressure can be seen in this.
Let's check out the Q4 results.  Let
us see before.
What dividend did the company declare?  Let us
also see how much dividend was declared.  The
company has recommended to the board that
shares will be available at ₹7 for ₹7.
What is the face value?  ₹10 See, it depends on the face value only.
If the face value of a company is
₹10, then according to ₹10,
its ₹7 is how much?
Dividend of 70% has been declared here.  Ok
?  So face value can understand
what is the face value of the company.  Ok?  So here we
talked about dividend and when will the dividend be
approved?  Approval will be given in SGMT.
Then after that the record date will come.  Then
after that the money will be credited to your account.
And when will the credit be given?  When you have
shares of ICIC Lambor in your demat account.
Let us now look at the
financial data.  What is the financial data
saying now?  Let's check out about that.
Talking about financial data here, let's
zoom out a little bit.
Now let's see what the result is.   Let me
scroll down a little bit.
Ok?  Now look here, the infection is clear.
Look, here whether we talk about gross premium
or net premium or
income investment.  Ok?
And talking about the total, if we see the total here, it
is around 62526 in this quarter of 31225
and if we see the previous quarter, it is
83, meaning the
result of this quarter has come out wrong in comparison to the previous quarter. If
we see it quarterly wise, it has taken a little hit on
this, okay, then after that 3124,
meaning if we compare it with the same quarter of last year,
this time's
quarter has come out wrong in that too, if we compare it year to year, it is
tremendous year to year, the
result has come out around 315 315 lakh crore 3 lakh 31590.  Meaning the
result is around 315590.  This means that the
company has announced good results.
Meaning year to year is good.  If we
talk about last year's 204, then it
is around 286.  Meaning, the year to year
results are good but he suffered a setback in the quarterly results.  The
quarterly results are messed up.  Keep
this thing in your mind.  Now let us
talk about profit and loss.  Ok?   Let's
talk about profit and loss here.
Profit Loss Has this announcement been made?   If we
talk about profit loss after tax, then
you should look into it.  Ok
?  Let's zoom in a little bit here.
Here you see, this is the profit
loss.  Ok?
Is around 50,959.  And last quarter
around 72,000.  Ok?  So, whenever
the revenue is less, the automatic profit
loss will also be less.  Ok?  And if we
look at the March quarter of the previous year 2024 of the same year, it was 91950,
okay, it was even less than that and if we look year to year, then year
to year what was the result of this year, it is
around 250 and
what was the result of this year, 191, that is, if we look at it year wise, then the
company has performed well, has
shown good growth, whereas
quarterly wise the growth of the company has
reduced, so if
we look at it quarterly growth wise, the growth of the company has reduced, so what will happen due to this is
that a
little pressure can be seen here.  But if you
look yearly then there is
no problem in the company.  You have given a good performance.  So here is
your quarterly result.
Quarterly Result Now you will see my feedback here.
Look at the feedback, one quarter does
not ruin a company.  It is such a big company.
Ok?  One quarter is bad, the next
quarter is good.  It continues like this.
Ok?  So here the company has shown
tremendous and very good growth year to year.
But here you can say that selling
pressure can also be seen tomorrow
because the quarterly results here
are messed up.  Again, there are no recommendations here for buying
or selling; information is being shared just for educational purposes.
Thank
you for watching this video.